# Lucas Dalan

Garça, São Paulo • +55 14 991944869 • lucasdalan09@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/lucasdalan

### **Software Engineer**

Full-stack developer with 4+ years of expertise building enterprise solutions, specializing in React.js and Typescript. Led the development of high-performance ERP systems, achieving 99.9% uptime and 20% efficiency gains. Known for mentoring developers while delivering complex projects ahead of schedule.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Harmonit 11/2023 - 10/2024 Software Engineer • Full-time

- Engineered and Implemented 5 ERP system features, reducing user navigation time by 40% and increasing customer satisfaction from 3.2 to 4.5 ou of 5.
- Enhanced user interface performance by 40% through the implementation of React, TypeScript, TailwindCSS, and other UI tools, resulting in improved user satisfaction and engagement.
- Led 12 agile sprints with a 95% on-time delivery rate, reducing project completion time.

## FRG Gestão Inteligente Software Engineer • Full-time

11/2021 - 11/2023

- Managed the Mosaic ERP project, leading to a streamlined development process and successful implementation, resulting in a 15% boost in productivity and client satisfaction.
- Mentored 2 junior developers, reducing code review iterations by 40% and improving sprint delivery times by 25%

### Trainee Developer • Internship

• Halved the number of software maintenance requests for the Mosaic ERP legacy project through proactive troubleshooting and code optimization.

DSIN - Solutions 01/2020 - 11/2020 Trainee Developer • Internship

- Mastered Git, CI/CD and the fundamentals of team development.
- Worked on a legacy system called SGIT, using Delphi as the main Framework.
- Strengthened interpersonal skills through active participation in team meetings, enabling smoother project workflows within a 2-month period.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor in Computer Science**

UNIVEM - Centro Universitário Eurípides Marília

Marília, São Paulo, Brasil

## **Course in English**

CCI - Centro de Comunicação Inglesa

### **SKILLS**

Hard Skills: API Rest, JavaScript, MySQL, Postgres, React.js, TypeScript

**Soft Skills:** Emotional Intelligence, Project Management, Software Engineer, Team

Management

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certificado Programação em Python do básico ao avançado